{
    "id": "1bd180abb0ea49e28873fbd8ea610379",
    "title": "Adjectives and adverbs quiz",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5d53b5d600e1477b90e78148d5e5602e",
            "title": "Adjectives And Adverbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The fish tasted …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "awful",
                        "awfully"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is …………………. cold.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bitter",
                        "bitterly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This novel is …………………. interesting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am ………………… glad to meet you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I could not find it ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "anywhere",
                        "nowhere"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The child ate the sweets …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "greedy",
                        "greedily"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You will pay …………………. for your mistakes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "dear",
                        "dearly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know ………………….. about him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "anything",
                        "nothing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t got ………………… money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "no"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was driving …………………. fast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unusual",
                        "unusually"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}